AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- School photo. 10 x 15 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1390)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 10 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1391)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 10.1 x 15 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1392)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, 1960/1970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1393)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 9.8 x 15.1 cm, 1960/1970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1394)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo. 10 x 15.2 cm, 1960/1970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1395)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 9.5 x 14 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1396)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- A group of men and clergymen in a house. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1397)
  Clergymen; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Women
- Two men checking a camera. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1398)
  Cameras; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- Entrance of a family tomb dating back to 1879. 14.5 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1399)
  Architecture; Cairo, Egypt; Cemeteries; Churches; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Tombs
- Italian letter about tombs by an archaeologist. 29.7 x 19.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1400)
  Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Envelope with a letter dating back to 14/2/1879. 10.4 x 14.6 cm, 20/2/1995; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1401)
  Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- Letter about a tomb affiliated with a Catholic mission to Egypt. 29.7 x 20.4 cm, 14/2/1879; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1402)
  Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Entrance of a family tomb. 14.5 x 10.1 cm, 1879; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1403)
  Architecture; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- A family tomb. 14.5 x 10.1 cm, 1879; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1404)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Construction in front of a family tomb. 14.6 x 10.1 cm, 1879; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1405)
  Color Photography; Construction; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Cemetery. 10.1 x 14.5 cm, 1879; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1406)
  Cemeteries; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Family tombs in a cemetery dating back to 1879. 14.5 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1407)
  Architecture; Cemeteries; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- The interior of a family tomb dating back to 1879. 14.5 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1408)
  Chairs; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Tombs; Windows
- Wedding ceremony in a church. 10.1 x 15.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1409)
  Churches; Clergymen; Color Photography; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Imagery; Wedding Ceremonies; Wedding Dresses; Women
- Man with a young woman in a house. 15.2 x 9.8 cm, 2003; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1410)
  Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits; Women
- Two women with an infant. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1411)
  Babies; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Women
- Two men and a woman. 9.8 x 15.1 cm, 2003; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1412)
  Color Photography; Computers; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Photo of two men in a house. 9.8 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1413)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- Two men and a young woman. 9.8 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1414)
  Color Photography; Computers; Furnishings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Individual portrait. 9.8 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1415)
  Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
- Historical pictures in a classroom. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, 1987-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1416)
  Classrooms; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Classroom. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, 1987-1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1417)
- Picture of a map of Egypt. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1418)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Maps; Photographic Prints
- Historical images of Helwan. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1419)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- Framed images of Paleolithic and Neolithic flints 4000/5000 BC. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1420)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Photographic Prints
- Framed images and map of Helwan. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1421)
- Framed images of Helwan. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1422)
- Map of the Royal Excavations at Helwan. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1423)
  Arabic Writing; Archaeological Sites; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Maps; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Historical map. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1424)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Maps; Photographic Prints
- Historical map of Helwan in 1888. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1425)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Maps; Photographic Prints
- Historical map of Helwan in 1930. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1426)
- Framed pictures of villas in Helwan. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1427)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Photographs
- Framed pictures of Helwan's bath houses taken in the 1800s. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1428)
  Arabic Writing; Baths; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Trees; Wall
- Framed pictures of Helwan's bath houses in the 1800s. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1429)
  Arabic Writing; Baths; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Wall
- Framed pictures of Helwan's bath houses in the 1800s. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1430)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Wall
- Historical map of Helwan in 1941. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1431)
- Framed pictures and floor plans of a monastery. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1432)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Color Photography; Deserts; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Monastery/Convent; Photographic Prints; Photographs
- Framed photographs. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1433)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Photographs
- Framed pictures. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1434)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Monuments; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Photographs
- Framed pictures. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1435)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Monuments; Photographic Prints; Photographs
- Framed pictures. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1436)
- Framed pictures, floor plans, and drawings. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1437)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Color Photography; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; History; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Wall
- Drawing of Pharaonic typography of Helwan. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1438)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; History; Maps; Photographic Prints; Wall
- Painting depicting ancient Egyptian deities Horus and Seth. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1439)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; Paintings; Photographic Prints; Wall
- Painting of Pharaoh Narmer's (or Menes) Palette. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1440)
  Arabic Writing; Art |x History; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Paintings; Photographic Prints
- Painting illustrating an ancient Egyptian story (?). 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1441)
  Arabic Writing; Art |x History; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Paintings; Photographic Prints
- Painting showing a place in Lower Egypt (Per Hapi). 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1442)
  Arabic Writing; Art |x History; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; Maps; Paintings; Photographic Prints
- Picture showing the school's priest's house. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 1890; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1443)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Color Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests
- Picture depicting a map. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, 1887; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1444)
  Art |x History; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Maps; Photographic Prints
- Picture depicting a map from 1887. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 1904; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1445)
  Art |x History; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Maps; Photographic Prints
- Picture of a museum's entrance. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1446)
  Color Photography; Desks; Helwan, Egypt; Museums; Photographic Prints
- Museum entrance behind desks. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1447)
- Picture depicting clocks made in 1869. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 2003; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1448)
  Clocks/Watches; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Museums; Photographic Prints
- Map of Helwan. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, 1917; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1449)
- Historical landscape pictures dating back to 2600 BC. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1450)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; History; Landscapes; Maps; Photographic Prints
- Picture of a headline from a newspaper clipping. 23.2 x 32.2 cm, 26 January 1930; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1451)
  Cairo, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Newspaper Clippings; Photographic Prints
- Picture depicting a church beside a car garage. 23.2 x 32.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1452)
  Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Factory; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Picture of a church. 32.2 x 23.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1453)
  Architecture; Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Image depicting a church. 32.2 x 23.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1454)
- Image of an altar at a church. 32.2 x 23.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1455)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Religious Imagery
- Picture showing an altar at a church. 32.2 x 23.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1456)
  Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Religious Imagery
- Image of a shrine of Virgin Mary. 32.2 x 23.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1457)
  Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Religious Imagery
- Shrine of a saint. 32.2 x 23.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1458)
- Image of an altar at a church. 23.2 x 32.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1459)
- Picture of a cross on a church's wall. 32.2 x 23.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1460)
- An altar at a church. 32.2 x 23.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1461)
- Students marching in front of their school., 1960; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1462)
  Boys; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Students in a classroom., 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1463)
  Boys; Classrooms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Students
- Family portrait., March 1971; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1464)
  Color Photography; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Students walking in the street., Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1465)
  Boys; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Students
- Group portrait of clergymen., 1948; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1466)
  Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints